http://www.accuride.com/privacy/

Your Online Privacy Matters To Us | Accuride International
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
For the best experience on our site, be sure to turn on Javascript in your browser.
Menu
ProductsDrawer SlidesSpecialty SlidesAccess ControlAccessoriesOnline Store
Light Duty
(139 LB. OR LESS)
Medium Duty
(140 TO 169 LB.)
Heavy Duty
(170 TO 1323 LB.)
Accuride Integrated Access Solutions
We don’t just supply movement for your designs – we also protect them. We offer innovative, discrete, and integrable electronic access control systems for your fixtures. Standalone or part of a broader access control network, we have the system for you.
LEARN MORE >
Accessories
Your go-to for kits, mounts, and extra parts for your sliding hardware. Whether it’s a bracket for special mounting or an Easy-Close dampener for a linear track, you’ll find the accessory you need here.
LEARN MORE >
Online Store
If your design needs movement, look no further! Our Online Store gives you access to Accuride's vast and proven range of premium movement solutions. From telescopic slides for kitchen cabinets to weather-resistant tracks outside fixtures, we have the right movement for your design.!
SHOP NOW >
Drawer Slides
Light Duty
(139 LB. OR LESS)
Medium Duty
(140 TO 169 LB.)
Heavy Duty
(170 TO 1323 LB.)Specialty Slides
Linear Track
Flipper Door Slides
Media Access
Keyboard Systems
Two-Way Travel
Tilt Track System
Pocket & Bayonet
Corrosion Resistant Slides
Access Control
Accuride Integrated Access Solutions
We don’t just supply movement for your designs – we also protect them. We offer innovative, discrete, and integrable electronic access control systems for your fixtures. Standalone or part of a broader access control network, we have the system for you.
LEARN MORE >
Accessories
Accessories
Your go-to for kits, mounts, and extra parts for your sliding hardware. Whether it’s a bracket for special mounting or an Easy-Close dampener for a linear track, you’ll find the accessory you need here.
LEARN MORE >
Online Store
Online Store
If your design needs movement, look no further! Our Online Store gives you access to Accuride's vast and proven range of premium movement solutions. From telescopic slides for kitchen cabinets to weather-resistant tracks outside fixtures, we have the right movement for your design.!
SHOP NOW >
MarketsAccess Control SystemsAerospace / WatercraftAppliancesArchitectural & DesignAutomation / Motion ControlAccess Control SystemsAerospace / WatercraftAppliancesArchitectural & DesignAutomation / Motion ControlAutomotiveConstruction / RailwayElectronic EnclosuresEmergency VehiclesHealthcareAutomotiveConstruction / RailwayElectronic EnclosuresEmergency VehiclesHealthcareHomeownersMachineryTransportationVending / Cash HandlingWoodworking & CabinetryHomeownersMachineryTransportationVending / Cash HandlingWoodworking & CabinetryAccess Control SystemsAerospace / WatercraftAppliancesArchitectural & DesignAutomation / Motion ControlAccess Control SystemsAerospace / WatercraftAppliancesArchitectural & DesignAutomation / Motion ControlAutomotiveConstruction / RailwayElectronic EnclosuresEmergency VehiclesHealthcareAutomotiveConstruction / RailwayElectronic EnclosuresEmergency VehiclesHealthcareHomeownersMachineryTransportationVending / Cash HandlingWoodworking & CabinetryHomeownersMachineryTransportationVending / Cash HandlingWoodworking & Cabinetry
How Accuride Drawer Slides are Revolutionizing Outdoor Living
Learn more >ResourcesAbout SlidesSlide GuidesVideosCADsFAQ'sLiterature
Slide Terminology
LEARN MORE >
Slide Components
LEARN MORE >
How to choose a slide
LEARN MORE >
Special slide features
LEARN MORE >
CAD Downloads
Need to see if one of our products will fit into your casework or millwork? Look no further: We have downloadable Computer-Aided Designs for all our slides, glides, and drawer runners.
LEARN MORE >
FAQs
Need to ID an Accuride slide? Find a replacement part? Browse are FAQ page for answers to those questions and more!
LEARN MORE >
Literature Request
Request a catalog or brochure for your industry. We have literature for manufacturers, craftsmen, and more.
READ MORE >
About Slides
Slide Terminology
LEARN MORE >
Slide Components
LEARN MORE >
Slide Guides
How to choose a slide
CAD Downloads
Need to see if one of our products will fit into your casework or millwork? Look no further: We have downloadable Computer-Aided Designs for all our slides, glides, and drawer runners.
LEARN MORE >
FAQ's
FAQs
Need to ID an Accuride slide? Find a replacement part? Browse are FAQ page for answers to those questions and more!
LEARN MORE >
Literature
Literature Request
Request a catalog or brochure for your industry. We have literature for manufacturers, craftsmen, and more.
READ MORE >
BlogIn Your IndustrySlideologyCustomer StoriesProducts
How Accuride Drawer Slides are Revolutionizing Outdoor Living
LEARN MORE >
Making the Home of the Future a Reality
LEARN MORE >
What is a Drawer Slide and How Do I Choose the Right One?
LEARN MORE >
What is a Drawer Slide?
LEARN MORE >
The Art of the Disconnect!
LEARN MORE >
How Accuride determines a Drawer Slide Load Rating
LEARN MORE >
Challenging Notions: Polish & Power Tools
LEARN MORE >
How Accuride Drawer Slides are Revolutionizing Outdoor Living
LEARN MORE >
Making the Home of the Future a Reality
LEARN MORE >
Linear Motion Track Systems: 115RC & 116RC
LEARN MORE >
Friction Guides: A Different Kind of Bold Movement
LEARN MORE >
AL4160: the New Super Heavy-Duty Slides
LEARN MORE >In Your Industry
How Accuride Drawer Slides are Revolutionizing Outdoor Living
LEARN MORE >
Making the Home of the Future a Reality
LEARN MORE >
What is a Drawer Slide and How Do I Choose the Right One?
LEARN MORE >Slideology
What is a Drawer Slide?
LEARN MORE >
The Art of the Disconnect!
LEARN MORE >
How Accuride determines a Drawer Slide Load Rating
LEARN MORE >Customer Stories
Challenging Notions: Polish & Power Tools
LEARN MORE >
How Accuride Drawer Slides are Revolutionizing Outdoor Living
LEARN MORE >
Making the Home of the Future a Reality
LEARN MORE >Products
Linear Motion Track Systems: 115RC & 116RC
LEARN MORE >
Friction Guides: A Different Kind of Bold Movement
LEARN MORE >
AL4160: the New Super Heavy-Duty Slides
LEARN MORE >SupportCustomer SupportShipping and ReturnsWarrantyHelp Center
Customer Support
Need help finding the right Accuride product? Want to check up on an order? Whatever your question, we’ll have the solution!
READ MORE >
Shipping and Returns
We offer multiple shipping methods. Upon placing an order we will provide a tracking number for your convenience. In the event that you have an issue with your order you can contact customer service for a return authorization. For more detailed information please read our full shipping and return policy.
LEARN MORE >
Warranty
Accuride warrants its Accuride–branded drawer slides against defects in material and workmanship for so long as the original purchaser owns them. *This warranty does not cover drawer slides which have been damaged due to abuse, improper installation, excessive loads, or any use contrary to the instructions accompanying the product.
READ MORE >
Customer Support
Customer Support
Need help finding the right Accuride product? Want to check up on an order? Whatever your question, we’ll have the solution!
READ MORE >
Shipping and Returns
Shipping and Returns
We offer multiple shipping methods. Upon placing an order we will provide a tracking number for your convenience. In the event that you have an issue with your order you can contact customer service for a return authorization. For more detailed information please read our full shipping and return policy.
LEARN MORE >
Warranty
Warranty
Accuride warrants its Accuride–branded drawer slides against defects in material and workmanship for so long as the original purchaser owns them. *This warranty does not cover drawer slides which have been damaged due to abuse, improper installation, excessive loads, or any use contrary to the instructions accompanying the product.
READ MORE >
Help CenterCompanyWho we areWhy AccurideTestimonialsNewsroomOEM DirectCareersEvents
Who we are
Founded as a small tool and die shop in 1958, Accuride has gone on to become a global designer and manufacturer of premium movement solutions. But we haven’t forgotten our roots: We’re still based in Santa Fe Springs, California, 50 years after we first moved there.
LEARN MORE >
Why Accuride?
Read up on the special features, technologies, and certifications that make Accuride unique and allow us to guarantee quality assurance for a wide range of applications.
LEARN MORE >
Santa Fe Springs Fire Department Solution
LEARN MORE >
Challenging Notions: Polish & Power Tools
LEARN MORE >
Beautifying Interior Movement: The Accuride 3160EC and 3832
LEARN MORE >
Accuride Launches Online Store
Join Our Team
Behind every great Accuride endeavor is a great team dedicated to quality and integrity
LEARN MORE >
Events
You can find Accuride at industry trade shows and expos across North America. Below you’ll find our calendar of scheduled events for the year. Please note our schedule may be subject to change.
LEARN MORE >
Who we are
Who we are
Founded as a small tool and die shop in 1958, Accuride has gone on to become a global designer and manufacturer of premium movement solutions. But we haven’t forgotten our roots: We’re still based in Santa Fe Springs, California, 50 years after we first moved there.
LEARN MORE >
Why Accuride
Why Accuride?
Read up on the special features, technologies, and certifications that make Accuride unique and allow us to guarantee quality assurance for a wide range of applications.
LEARN MORE >
Testimonials
Santa Fe Springs Fire Department Solution
LEARN MORE >
Challenging Notions: Polish & Power Tools
LEARN MORE >
Beautifying Interior Movement: The Accuride 3160EC and 3832
LEARN MORE >Newsroom
Join Our Team
Behind every great Accuride endeavor is a great team dedicated to quality and integrity
LEARN MORE >
Events
Events
You can find Accuride at industry trade shows and expos across North America. Below you’ll find our calendar of scheduled events for the year. Please note our schedule may be subject to change.
LEARN MORE >
StoreOnline StoreOEMDistributor
Online Store
If your design needs movement, look no further! Our Online Store gives you access to Accuride's vast and proven range of premium movement solutions. From telescopic slides for kitchen cabinets to weather-resistant tracks outside fixtures, we have the right movement for your design.!
SHOP NOW >
OEM DIRECT
Accuride is more than a global manufacturer: We’re a trusted partner with a renowned team of experts who can provide you with the most comprehensive assemblage of custom and off-the-shelf movement solutions for any market.
CONTACT OEM DIRECT >
Distributors
Accuride works with trusted distributors throughout the globe. Find the one closest to you!
LEARN MORE >
Online Store
Online Store
If your design needs movement, look no further! Our Online Store gives you access to Accuride's vast and proven range of premium movement solutions. From telescopic slides for kitchen cabinets to weather-resistant tracks outside fixtures, we have the right movement for your design.!
SHOP NOW >
OEM
OEM DIRECT
Accuride is more than a global manufacturer: We’re a trusted partner with a renowned team of experts who can provide you with the most comprehensive assemblage of custom and off-the-shelf movement solutions for any market.
CONTACT OEM DIRECT >
Distributor
Distributors
Accuride works with trusted distributors throughout the globe. Find the one closest to you!
LEARN MORE >
Account
Search
Search
Compare Products
My Cart
Privacy
Privacy Policy
Accuride International Inc. (“Accuride”) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy (‘Policy’) (together with our Terms of Use contains important information about who we are, how and why we collect, store, use and share personal information, your rights in relation to your information and on how to contact us and supervisory authorities in the event you have a complaint. By visiting www.accuride.com (our “Site”) you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.
Accuride (“we” or “us”) collects, uses and is responsible for certain personal information about you. This information may include: your name, company name, credit card information, banking account information, email address, physical address, and phone number(s). You may choose not to provide certain information, but this may prevent you from utilizing some features of our Site. The information you provide may be used for purposes such as responding to your requests, proactively communicating with you, improving your future Site experiences, and improving our Site.
Personal Data we may collect about you
We do not obtain personal identifying information about you when you visit our Site.
We will collect and process the following data about you:
Information you give us: This is information about you that you give us by communicating with us by phone, e-mail, on-line chat or otherwise. It includes information you provide when you register to use our Site and if you place an order on our Site. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address and any marketing preferences that you specify.
Information we collect about you: With regard to each of your visits to our Site we will automatically collect information about your visit, including name of the domain from which you accessed the Internet, the date and time you accessed our Site,your IPaddress and cookiesand the pages you retrieved from our Site. We collect this information to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our Site, and to help us make the Site more useful to visitors.
How long your personal data will be kept: We will hold the information you give us and the information we collect about you until you unsubscribe from our mailing lists or we get a failure message by way of return to any marketing communication that we send to you.
Cookies
Our website uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of our website. This helps us to provide you with a personalized experience when you browse our website and also allows us to improve our Site. For detailed information on the cookies we use and the purposes for which we use them see our Cookie Policy.   Reasons we can collect and use your personal information We will process your personal data in accordance with applicable laws and regulations. We will use your personal data for the purposes that we identified to you at the time your data was obtained. These purposes may include:
to help us identify you • research, statistical analysis and behavioural analysis
marketing
improving our services
Disclosure of your information
You agree that we have the right to share your personal information with:
our agents, service providers
law enforcement agencies in connection with any investigation to help prevent unlawful activity
Interest Based Advertising
We participate in interest-based advertising and use third party on-line advertising networks, social media companies and other third party service providers to send you targeted advertisements based on your browsing history. We permit these companies to collect information about your use of our Site and mobile apps.  Our third party partners and we use this information to make the advertisements more relevant to your interests, as well as to provide reporting, attribution, analytics and market research. See Opt Out below, to learn more about how you may control interest-based advertising.
Social Media
Our Site may include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button, Google Plus, LinkedIn, Snapchat, Instagram, Twitter or other widgets. These social media companies may recognize you and collect information about your visit to our Site, and they may set a cookie or employ other tracking technologies. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of those companies.
Your information collected through our website may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Accuride, our affiliates or service providers maintain facilities.  This applies to all visitors to our Site (including those who reside outside the United States) who provide us with personal information.
The data that we collect from you will be processed by staff who work for us or for one of our suppliers. This includes staff engaged in, among other things: marketing/advertising activities, the fulfillment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of sales and support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.
For visitors to our Site who reside outside the United States, the data protection and privacy laws of other countries, including the United States, may not afford you the same level of protection as those in your own country.  Accuride will take appropriate steps to protect your information. By doing business or interacting with us, you are consenting to the transfer, storage and processing of your information to and within facilities located in the United States and other facility locations selected by us. If you would like further information please contact, our Data Protection Officer dpo-us@accuride.com.
Keeping your data secure
We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorized way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorized manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Site. Any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.
Assumption of Risk
By using this Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Children’s Privacy
We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 13 on this Site. In the event that we learn that we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under 13, please contact us at dpo-us@accuride.comMarketing and your rightsWe may send company news and information to you if you have:
expressly shared your postal or email address for the purpose of receiving information in the future; or
purchased from or have an existing relationship with us.
You can opt out at any time. Our email correspondence will include instructions to allow you to request to be removed from our future mailing list.
Opt Out
Our users are given the opportunity to "Opt Out" of having their personal information disclosed, used or distributed to third-parties and the opportunity to "Opt Out" of having us use the personal information for a purpose which is incompatible with the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the User. To "Opt Out" please request by e-mail to dpo-us@accuride.com.
How to Contact Us
We hope that our Data Protection Officer can resolve any inquiry or concern you raise about our use of your information.If you wish to access, verify or change your personal information, please write to:Data Protection OfficerAccuride International Inc.12311 Shoemaker AvenueSanta Fe Springs, California 90670Email:  dpo-us@accuride.com
California Consumer Privacy Act
If you are a California resident, please click here CCPA for more information about how we collect, use and share your personal information and the rights you have with respect to your personal information.
Changes to our privacy policy
This privacy notice was published on January 1, 2020. Any changes we make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. We may change this privacy notice from time to time. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
California Privacy Policy (CCPA)
Your California Privacy Rights
This California Privacy Rights Disclosure (the "Disclosure") supplements Accuride’s Privacy Policy by describing your privacy rights as a California resident ("you") and including information on how to exercise your rights. Accuride’s Privacy Policy describes the personal information that we collect, the sources from which we collect it, the purposes for which we use it, the circumstances under which we share personal information, and with whom we share it.
The California Consumer Privacy Act (“Act”) requires these additional disclosures:
A.
Categories of Personal Information Collected.
The personal information that Accuride collects or has collected from consumers in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure, fall into the following categories established by the Act:
Identifiers such as you name, company name, address, phone numbers, or e-mail address;
Personal information, such as a credit card or banking account information;
Age, gender, or other protected classifications
Communications and interactions, which may include email messages, chat sessions, and phone calls that we exchange with you;
Demographic information, which may include age or birthdate, gender, ZIP code, your status as a Loyalty Club member, and other information about you;
Call recordings, including information about your call and that you share when you call us on the phone;
Device and browsing information and other Internet activity information, including information about your phone, tablet, computer, or device, and online browsing activity (collectively, "automatically collected information"). Automatically collected information may include IP addresses, unique device identifiers, cookie identifiers, device and browser settings and information, and Internet service provider information. Automatically collected information also may include information about when and how you access and use our website or mobile application, such as the date and time of your visit or use, the websites you visit before coming and after leaving our website, how you navigate and what you search for using our website and mobile application, the website pages and items you view using our website and mobile application, and the items you purchase;
B.
Categories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business Purpose.
The business information that Accuride disclosed about consumers for a business purpose in the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure fall into the following categories established by the Act:
Identifiers such as your name, address, phone numbers, or e-mail address, for example if we use a third party carrier to deliver your order;
Personal information, such as a credit card, for example if we use a third party payment processor;
Your age, gender, or other protected classifications, for example if you choose to participate in a survey distributed by a survey provider;
Call recordings, including information about your call and that you share when you call us on the phone;
C.
No Sale of Personal Information.
In the twelve months prior to the effective date of this Disclosure Accuride has not sold any personal information of consumers, as those terms are defined under the Act.
D.
Right to Request Access to or Deletion of Personal Information or Opt-Out of Sale of Personal Information.
You may submit your request through the following methods:
Send an inquiry to dpo-us@accuride.com to request access to your personal data or deletion of your personal data
Send an inquiry to dpo-us@accuride.com to Opt-Out of the sale of your personal data
By phone at (562) 372-6978
E.
No Discrimination.
Accuride will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the Act.
F.
Effective Date.
This disclosure is effective January 1, 2020.
Terms Of Use
Please read these Terms of Use carefully before using this site1. General 1.1  Who we are and how to contact uswww.accuride.com (the “Site”)is a Site operated by;Accuride International Inc.12311 Shoemaker Avenue, Santa Fe Springs, California 90670The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our Site.To contact us, please email websupport@accuride.com1.2  By using our Site you accept these Terms of UseBy using our Site, you confirm that you accept these Terms of Use and that you agree to comply with them. If you do not agree to these terms, you must not use our Site.1.3  There are other terms that may apply to youThese Terms of Use refer to the following additional terms, which also apply to your use of our Site:• Our Privacy Policy, which sets out the terms on which we process any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us. By using our Site, you consent to such processing and you warrant that all data provided by you is accurate.• Our Cookie Policy, which sets out information about the cookies on our Site.2. Use of the Site2.1  We amend these terms from time to time. Every time you wish to use our Site, please check these terms to ensure you understand the terms that apply at that time.2.2  We may update and change our Site. We aim to update our Site regularly and may change the content from time to time. Any of the material on our Site may be out of date at any given time and we shall be under no obligation to update such material.No changes to these terms and conditions are valid or have any effect unless agreed by us in writing. We reserve the right to vary these terms and conditions from time to time. Our new terms and conditions will be displayed on our Site and by continuing to use and access the Site following such changes, you agree to be bound by any variation made by us. It is your responsibility to check these terms and conditions and take notice of any changes we have made.3. Accessing our Site3.1  Our Site is made available free of charge. We reserve the right to withdraw or amend the service we provide on our Site without notice.3.2  We do not guarantee that our Site, or any content on it, will always be available or be uninterrupted. We may suspend or withdraw or restrict the availability of all or any part of our Site for business and operational reasons.3.3  You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access our Site through your internet connection are aware of these Terms of Use and other applicable terms and conditions, and that they comply with them.3.4  Furthermore, we reserve the right to bar users or customers from access to either our Site and any services contained within where a user or customer commits or seeks to commit fraud or attempts to disrupt in any way the services offered by us.3.5  You must keep your account details safe.If you choose, or you are provided with, a user identification code, password or any other piece of information as part of our security procedures, you must treat such information as confidential. You must not disclose it to any third party.We have the right to disable any user identification code or password, whether chosen by you or allocated by us, at any time, if in our reasonable opinion you have failed to comply with any of the provisions of these terms of use.If you know or suspect that anyone other than you know your user identification code or password, you must promptly notify us by email. 4.    Intellectual Property Rights4.1  How you may use material on our SiteWe are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in our Site, and in the material published on it.  Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved.You may print off one copy, and may download extracts, of any page(s) from our Site for your personal use and you may draw the attention of others within your organisation to content posted on our Site.You must not modify the paper or digital copies of any materials you have printed off or downloaded in any way, and you must not use any illustrations, photographs, video or audio sequences or any graphics separately from any accompanying text.Our status and that of any identified contributors as the authors of content on our Site must always be acknowledged.You must not use any part of the content on our Site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors.If you print off, copy or download any part of our Site in breach of these terms of use, your right to use our Site will cease immediately and you must, at our option, return or destroy any copies of the materials you have made. 5.    Hyperlinks and third party websites5.1  Where our Site contains links to other Sites and resources provided by third parties, these links are provided for your information only. Such links should not be interpreted as approval by us of those linked websites or information you may obtain from them. We have no control over the contents of those Sites or resources.6. Our Liability6.1  Under this clause 6, we do not exclude or limit in any way our liability to you where it would be unlawful to do so. This includes liability for death or personal injury caused by our negligence or the negligence of our employees, agents or subcontractors and for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation.6.2  Different limitations and exclusions of liability will apply to liability arising as a result of the supply of any products to you, which will be set out in our General Terms and Conditions of Sales.6.3  We exclude all implied conditions, warranties, representations or other terms that may apply to our Site or any content on it.6.4  We will not be liable to you for any loss or damage that arise from relying on any content displayed on our Site or where you decide to act or not to act based upon the information contained on our Site.6.5  Any content on our Site is provided for your general information purposes only and to inform you about us and our products and services that may be of interest.6.6  To the extent permitted by law, we hereby expressly exclude any liability for (i) any economic loss (loss of profits, sales, business, or revenue), (ii) business interruption, (iii) any loss of goodwill and reputation, or (iv) any indirect or consequential loss or damage incurred by any user in connection with our Site.6.7  Our liability for any loss or damage is limited to that which is a reasonably foreseeable consequence by a breach of these Terms of Use. Losses are foreseeable where they could be contemplated by you and us at the time these terms and conditions were entered into. 7.    Uploading content to our Site7.1  Whenever you make use of a feature that allows you to upload content to our Site, you warrant that it does not contain any material which infringes any copyright, database right or trade mark of any other person, or cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety or any other material of this nature.7.2  You warrant that any such contribution does comply with those standards, and you will be liable to us and indemnify us for any breach of that warranty. This means you will be responsible for any loss or damage we suffer as a result of your breach of warranty.7.3  We will not be responsible, or liable to any third party, for the content or accuracy of any materials posted by you or any other user of our Site.7.4  We also have the right to disclose your identity to any third party who is claiming that any content posted or uploaded by you to our Site constitutes a violation of their intellectual property rights, or of their right to privacy.7.5  You are solely responsible for securing and backing up your content.8.    Viruses, Hacking and other Offences8.1  We are not responsible for viruses and you must not introduce themWe do not guarantee that our Site will be secure or free from bugs or viruses. You are responsible for configuring your information technology, computer programmes and platform to access our Site. You should use your own virus protection software.You must not misuse our Site by knowingly introducing viruses, trojans, worms, logic bombs or other material that is malicious or technologically harmful. You must not attempt to gain unauthorized access to our Site, the server on which our Site is stored or any server, computer or database connected to our Site. You must not attack our Site via a denial-of-service attack or a distributed denial-of service attack.
Cookie Policy
What are cookies?
A cookie is a small file containing a text that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. When you visit the website again, the cookie allows that site to recognize your browser.
Why we use cookies
Cookies may store user preferences and other information. This allows us to personalize & improve your experience.
Cookie Preferences
You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some website features or services may not function properly without cookies.
Types of cookies we may use:
Preferences
These cookies allow our websites to remember information that changes the way the site behaves or looks, such as your preferred language or the region you are in.
Security
We use security cookies to authenticate users, prevent fraudulent use of login credentials, and protect user data from unauthorized parties.
Processes
Process cookies help make the website work and deliver services that the website visitor expects, like navigating around web pages or accessing secure areas of the website.
Advertising
We use cookies to make advertising more engaging for users.
Session
Web collect information about how our users interact with our website. This may include the pages users visit most often and whether users get error messages from certain pages.
Please enable JavaScript.
subscribe
Sending...
©2020 ACCURIDE INTERNATIONAL INC.
